See the music. Hear the dance.
High Strung is a music, romance, drama film directed by Michael Damian.
When a hip hop violinist busking in the New York subway encounters a classical dancer
on scholarship at the Manhattan Conservatory of the Arts, sparks fly.
With the help of a hip hop dance crew they must find a common ground while
preparing for a competition that could change their lives forever.
Ruby, played by Keenan Kampa.
Johnnie, played by Nicholas Galitzine.
Jazzy, played by Sonoya Mizuno.
Oksana, played by Jane Seymour.
Kyle, played by Richard Southgate.
Kramrovsky, played by Paul Freeman.
High Strung is a 2016 American drama film directed by Michael
Damian and written by Janeen Damian and Michael Damian.
The film stars Keenan Kampa, Nicholas Galitzine, Jane Seymour,
Sonoya Mizuno, Richard Southgate, and Paul Freeman.
The film was released on April 8, 2016, by Paladin.
A sequel High Strung: Free Dance was released in 2019.
The film explores themes of dance, violin, ballet, leotard.
The tone is emotional.